# 在柳州吃过螺蛳粉
I have eaten snail noodle in Liuzhou
# 在桂林吃过米粉
And rice noodle in Guilin
# 今天我们来尝一尝南昌的米粉是什么样子
Let’s try rice noodle in Nanchang
# 江西 南昌
Nanchang, Jiangxi
# 哎呀 这队伍都堵到门口了
Aiya, customers are lining up to the door
# 站在队伍的最后
Sit on the end of the line
# 正是考验视力的时候
It's time to test eyesight
# 让我看看这的拌粉都有什么样子的
let me take a look at the Banfen
# 这米粉可以和很多种肉拌一起
Rice noodle can be mixed with a lot of types of meat
# 像牛肉啊 猪肚 猪肝都是可以的
Like beef or pork belly, and pork liver
# 也可以把几种肉混合一起拌
Or mixed them together
# 价格会更高
It will be more expensive
# 我要一个牛肉拌粉 就这些
I want a beef Banfen, that’s all
# 她们是5个人拿着五个盆拌粉 好壮观啊
Five people are mixing five pots at same time
# 凉拌粉
Cold mixed rice noodle
# 要香菜吗？
Add cilantro?
# 要 所有的料都要
Yeah, all of the ingredients
# 南昌人都喜欢吃粉 早餐就是拌粉
Nanchang people love to eat rice noodle so much even eat it as breakfast
# 拌粉就是米粉加各种菜、调料
Mixed rice noodle is mix rice noodle with different dishes and seasonings
# 我今天点的是13元的牛肉拌粉
I ordered 13 yuan beef mixed rice noodle
# 加了花生 萝卜这些配菜 上面铺满了牛肉
With toppings like pickled peanut and radish, and beef on it
# 看起来真的很不错
Looks pretty good
# 这碗粉几乎是一半粉一半料
Almost half of ingredients and half of rice noodle in a bowl
# 看起来好好吃啊
Looks so delicious
# 我发现除了牛肉 香菜比较多之外
I found out that
# 还有更多的辣椒
And more red pepper
# 江西人喜欢吃辣
Jiangxi people like spicy food
# 连早上最快捷的一餐也不会放过辣椒
Even eat it in the fastest meal in a day, which is breakfast
# 这么一闻都能闻着辣味
I can smell spicy now
# 这里有红辣椒 绿辣椒 还有蒜末
There is red pepper, green pepper and minced garlic
# 这个米粉感觉很厚实
This rice noodle looks pretty thick
# 用筷子一夹 感觉沉甸甸的
It feels heavy to use chopstick to narrow it
# 看这大片的牛肉 我都等不及要吃了
I can’t wait to eat in front of huge slices of beef
# 第一口是牛肉 蒜末 有点辣味 咸味略淡
The first bite with beef, minced garlic, a little bit spicy and light salty
# 这个米粉一夹还感觉特别爽滑
This rice noodle feels very tender and smoothy
# 和大片牛肉一起吃 绝配啊
It’s a great combo to eat with beef
# 吃起来好爽滑
Very tender and smoothy
# 里面是不是加了香油啊 感觉好香啊
Does it add sesame oil? Smells so fragment
# 这个牛肉是沾满了辣椒和蒜的 吃起来特别开胃
This beef is soaked in chili and minced garlic. It tastes very appetizing.
# 辣椒是新鲜辣椒 辣度是直击灵魂的辣
Fresh red pepper is pretty spicy
# 吃到最后 还有这么多的料啊
The are a lot of ingredients left at the end
# 感觉有把火往胃里烧（好辣）
My stomach are burning(so spicy)
# 真想对着空调吹吹嘴
I want use air conditioning to blow my mouth
# 我去年11月份时候来过南昌一次
I visited Nanchang once in November last year
# 在这边吃了三顿饭 感觉承受不了这样的辣度
And ate 3 meals, all too spicy for me
# 结果呢就是视频也没有发
And i didn’t post any videos about it
# 今年呢再来一次南昌挑战一下日常吃饭的辣度
I want to challenge it again this year
# 这是打包带走的
This is for take out
# 这个是自己带保温饭盒来的
This is bring his own Thermal lunch box
# 辣椒香菜要吗
Add red pepper and
# 一碗要一碗不要
Red pepper and cilantro for one bowl
# 看很多本地人来吃拌粉的时候
Local people come to eat mixed rice noodle
# 都会要一碗猪肝鸡蛋汤
With pork liver and egg soup
# 像我的饭量 吃一碗米粉就饱了
I will get full with one bowl of rice noodle
# 吃完感觉好辣啊
So spicy
# 唯一不好的地方是里面加了蒜
The only bad part is that it adds garlic
# 这大早上的啊
What a morning!